Just to finish, how do you think this
plays out with Russia? Like how What do
you What do you think happens,
especially if you take it all the way up
to the election?
At the CIA, in our analysis, we used to
use this term all the time, muddling
through. Um you know, is so many so many
people just naturally their brain
defaults to an either or
uh
choice
when they when they try to
prognosticate. And oftentimes what was
true was that the parties in a conflict
just sort of muddled through and things
just didn't change over the medium term.
And I think that that's what we're
looking at here. The Russians aren't
going to aren't going to use nuclear
weapons. I don't think they'll even use
tactical nuclear weapons because they'll
lose the propaganda advantage of saying,
"Look, the only country in the history
of the planet that's ever used nuclear
weapons is the United States and they
did it twice."
Right? They don't want to be lumped in
with that. They want to be able to
continue to point at the United States
like they've done since 1945.
Um they don't need to use nuclear
weapons, even tactical ones. Uh now they
have a virtually unlimited supply of of
suicide drones that they're getting from
both the Chinese and the Iranians and
are attempting to purchase from the from
the Indians. And so, what's better than
a small payload on a on a drone that
costs you $14,000
rather than the you know, 100,000 or
200,000 that American missiles cost? And
you can just lob them into buildings or
into military bases or onto airfields.
I think that they're just going to
continue to do that. I think we'll see a
slight upgrade in the level of uh of
Russian technology that they're able to
either develop or to purchase on the
open market. I think that here in the
United States we'll continue to arm and
and to train the Ukrainians in
basically whatever they want
up to and including the F-16.
And then I think as we approach the
American elections,
the Republicans are going to have a real
campaign issue
uh going home and saying,
"Why should we be paying for all this?
We have bridges falling into the rivers
below them. We have international
airports that are international
embarrassments for anybody who's ever
traveled around the world. We have an an
interstate highway system that would
take a trillion dollars to repair.
And we want to move the world's
microchip manufacturing out of uh
out of Taiwan and Singapore and into
Ohio and uh and Arizona
with what money?
With the money that we're sending to to
Ukraine?
This has to come to a stop.
And God knows already our our NATO
allies don't want to pay for it. They're
They're uh
Their national debts as a as a function
of GDP are worse than ours.
They want us to pay for it. And so I
think we'll we'll muddle through the
short term and maybe the medium term and
then it's going to become a political
issue here in the United States where
where American voters just say, "Look,
enough. Enough with this. We don't want
to pay for it anymore. This has to be
settled." And I think eventually it will
be. You know, we a lot of us said this
at the very beginning, too, and I I
should repeat this.
Um I think in the end
the Russians are going to keep uh
Donetsk and Luhansk. They're going to
keep the Crimea.
There will be a promise that Ukraine
will not join NATO.
But the United States will declare
Ukraine a major non-NATO ally like
Israel or Japan or Bahrain or Saudi
Arabia.
And uh
Ukraine will be fast-tracked for
membership in the European Union. I
think that's how this ends.
Hm.
And do you think this could lose
the uh Biden the re-election? Or do you
think with all the propaganda going on,
it will not be a major enough issue for
people to say enough is enough?
I don't think it'll be enough of an
issue. I think it's going to drag on
longer than that. I think it's going to
drag on through the election. Now, if
Joe Biden were able to run for for
election again in in 2028, which of
course he's not, even if he were to be
alive in 2028,
um
I think by 2028 everybody's going to be
sick of this. But I think 2024 is
practically upon us. And
you know, look look around. I I'm I'm
looking over for example, uh right now
as we speak, McPherson not McPherson
Square, but uh but Farragut Square. I'm
one block from the White House. And
we're not seeing people in the streets.
We're not seeing people marching with
signs and placards saying, you know, end
the war. We're not. People are just
going about their normal business like
they generally don't care
because it doesn't affect them directly.
But when we have to
keep raising taxes
uh to pay for these weapons systems, and
all this money goes to US defense
contractors, and they get rich while you
and I get poor,
and we continue to neglect our
infrastructure,
then finally I think people are going to
get sick of this. So, Jim Rickards has
just recorded a video [music] that's not
available to anyone in the public, and
he's going to be talking about how this
upcoming recession [music] is going to
be fast, it's going to be bloody, it's
going to be nasty. But at the same time,
he's going to show you how you can
position yourself to profit from all of
this chaos. Now, we've made this video
[music]
only available to our viewers. Go to
londonreal.tv/jim.
Watch that immediately. I can't [music]
say enough good things about Jim
Rickards. He understands the global
economic system better than any guest
I've ever had on London Real. His
predictions [music] are almost uncannily
true, and you can learn how to profit
from his vision, from his expertise, and
his understanding [music] of economics.
So, go to londonreal.tv/jim
or click the link below. It's an
excellent, excellent look on what's
going to happen [music] in the future
and how you can position yourself to
profit from that. Jim is one of the best
in the business, one of my favorite
guests [music] on London Real, and he's
very, very good at predicting the future
and showing us all to profit from it.
So, click the link, and I hope you
enjoy.
I'm looking for partners, collaborators,
[music]
colleagues who want to join forces with
me around the globe and create real
value,
>> [music]
>> generational wealth, and financial
freedom for everyone else around the
world.
>> [music]
>> Get involved in the cryptocurrency
markets. Get involved in the NFT
markets. This is your moment. Life all
[music] comes down to a few moments.
Don't let this pass. Now, it's not too
late. Next year's going to be too late.
Ultimately, this is about freedom.
That's the way I see it. This is about
giving power [music] back to the people
and enabling billions of people
worldwide to use the financial markets
to improve their lives and those of
their friends and their families and
their communities.
Honestly, I think it's a violation of
human rights not to allow people basic
access to financial services. Because
right now, people are being kept in the
dark. They're being robbed of education,
and it's a travesty. And [music] so, I'm
looking for people that want to join me
and be a part of the solution and that
all happens inside the Dfy Academy.
The gains my students are making are
absolutely amazing. Double, triple digit
gains in the first month alone. That's
amazing. This will change your life.
>> [music]
>> Now is the time to get involved. I'm
going to tell you exactly how my
students
in [music] my academy made money in the
last 30 days. I'm talking about real
trading results.
>> [music]
>> So let me just wet your appetite a
little bit. Let me hit you with some
numbers. I'm talking Brandon from New
Zealand is up 68.77%
on the month. Steve from Europe up 83%
Albert in Singapore up 169.9%
on one single trade. I got Susan up 153%
on her call options alone. Also rocking
139% returns and 442%
returns as well on individual trades.
These are people that are changing their
financial future in the last 30 days,
but it's based on trading discipline.
I've graduated over 500 students from
inside my academy from over 54 countries
around the world. It's amazing.
When it comes to crypto, Dfy, and
blockchain, we love this space.
>> [music]
>> We truly believe it's the future. This
is down to our core. It's authentic to
what we're doing
>> [music]
>> and everybody can tell through the
camera because you can't make this stuff
up.
If you're watching me now, wherever you
are, I implore you take 60 seconds right
now and join my academy. Apply today.
Now you've got a chance. Life all comes
down to a few moments. What are you
going to do? What's the choice that
you're going to make?